If I ever go to sleep thinking that I have to
wake up early tomorrow.  But still I am unable to get up.  That's
why my day starts very
late.  And the first thing
I do when I wake up is drink these Amla shots.
For this I warm water in a tea pot.
Then I put two to three cubes in a cup,
add lukewarm water to it and
drink it.  And friend, its taste is
very bad.  The
mood also gets spoiled early in the morning.  But it is
good for skin and hair.  That's why we have to drink
and yesterday everyone had applied mehndi at
night itself.  But yesterday I was working till late night due to which
I did
not apply mehendi yesterday and I did not have
time right now so I thought I would apply
mehendi before taking bath.  Anyway, I knew that
I was going to apply very bad mehndi
and my grandmother also came to see me applying mehndi.
Then I
applied mehndi to my grandmother also.  After that, I stood under the fan for 5 to 6 minutes and
dried my henna.  After that I went to take a bath and
I felt that this mehndi would
not stick at all.  But by evening
its colour had become very dark.
After that, as soon as I came back after taking bath.  I
made the halwa first and then it got quite
late.  So that's why I thought I should
wear nice clothes and since it was Teej today,
I wore this green suit which
I will tag here.  Then
I did not do heavy makeup but
kept it very light.  So that's all for today, see you
in the next blog.  Bye bye.